{"data":[{"question":"Mr. Jefferson's students ___ busily when he went to get his handouts he ___ in the office.","a":"were writing, has left","b":"had written, left","c":"were writing, had left","d":"had written, had left","answer":"3","explain":"\n- First blank: past continuous tense (Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past (went to) \n+ Past continuous tense, when simple past \n- Second blank: past perfect tense:The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past. \n+ Past Perfect, when simple past tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Sandra ___ into Amanda's room when no one ___.","a":"had slipped, looked","b":"slipped, was looking","c":"was slipping, looked","d":"slipped, had looked","answer":"2","explain":"\n- First blank: simple past tense \n+ Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action (was looking) in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past (slipped) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"If city noises ___ from increasing, people ___ shout to be heard even at the dinner table in the future.","a":"are not kept, have to","b":"are not kept, will have to","c":"do not keep, have to","d":"do not keep, will have to","answer":"2","explain":"\n-Zero Conditional: used for habitual actions or accepted facts\nIt is created by if\/when simple present tense, simple present tense\/ simple future tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We could have walked to the department store; it was so near. \"Yes. A motorcycle ___ at all necessary.\"","a":"hadn't been","b":"wasn't","c":"won't be","d":"wouldn't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you know our center at all? \"No, this is the first time I ___ here.\"","a":"am going","b":"was","c":"have been","d":"came","answer":"3","explain":"\n- This is the first time + perfect (present\/past) tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When I was at college I ___ four foreign languages, but I ___ all except a few words of each.","a":"spoke, have forgotten","b":"spoke, had forgotten","c":"had spoken, have forgotten","d":"had spoken, had forgotten","answer":"1","explain":"\n- First blank: simple past tense \n- Second blank: Present continuous tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Come on in, Kevin. We want to show you something. \"Oh, how nice of you guys! I ___ you ___ to bring me a present.\"","a":"never thought, were going","b":"never think, are going","c":"hadn't thought, were going","d":"didn't think, were going","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple Past :used to describe past facts or generalizations which are no longer true \n+ Be going to","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Has Jeff moved into his new house? \"Not yet. The rooms ___\"","a":"are painting","b":"are being painted","c":"are being painting","d":"are painted","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present continuous tense - passive voice: be being pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I haven't heard from Morris for a long time. \"What do you suppose ___ to him?","a":"to happen","b":"was happening","c":"having happened","d":"has happened","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense:We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"On Tuesday morning, Ms. Meng went to the market, ___ some tomatoes and visited her uncle.","a":"buying","b":"bought","c":"buy","d":"to buy","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: We use the Simple Past to list a series of completed actions in the past.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}